hikarabita kotoba wo tsunai de
connecting old words that have been used up
soredemo bokura shinpuru na omoi wo tsutaetai dake na no
I just want to convey my simple thoughts
fukinukeru kusunda ano hi no kaze wa
that day's faint wind blows away
kinou no haikyo ni uchi sutete
at the castle ruins of yesterday
kimi to warau ima wo ikiru no da
I'll laugh with you and live for the moment
soredemo ano dekigoto ga kimi wo kurushimeru daro
still that incident will continue to trouble you, right?
dakarakoso sayonara nanda
that's why it must be good-bye
konomama nanimo nokorazu ni anata to wakachiau dake
leaving nothing behind, let us share what is left
yagate bokura wa sore ga subetee dato kigatsuite
in time, we'll realize that it was everything
kanashimi wa hoo wo tsutatte namida no kawa ni naru dake
and sadness will touch our cheeks, creating a river of tears
yureru omoi wa tsuyoi uzu ni natte tokeau no yo
Trembling thoughts swept into a vortex and melting away
{Roar! Howl!
{The Ultimate Tag
Yahoo!
Got you!
Damn!
What's going on?!
I felt a response to my attack
but it didn't work.
And where did his attack
come from?
Listen, Akamaru.
We're gonna attack from both sides
with Fang Over Fang.
Here we go!
Fang Over Fang!
Summoning Jutsu!
This doesn't look so good.
I'll play a melody of death for you.
What's with this guy?
What?!
Two on two is perfect
right, Sakon?
How could the Sound Ninja Four
take so much time?
Did they send such strong people
after them who could hold them up...
or are they playing around too much?
Well, the one that's probably
delaying things is...
either Jirobo who gets hungry a lot
or Kidomaru who likes to play.
But the one that's
the most dangerous
when he loses his temper
is Sakon.
He's not satisfied until
he kills his opponent
even though he should
just leave things be.
He thinks he's the strongest of
the four so he shows off.
I wonder if that's so...
Tayuya has a personality that's
neck and neck with Sakon.
But in any case,
nothing bad will happen
since we sent that kid...
Kimimaro.
He'll surely clean up anything that is
not good for me.
I will never let you take Sasuke!
There's a lot of trash scattered about.
But after all trash is trash.
It simply needs to be cleaned up.
Shut up!
Come on.
I'll crush you!
So this is the so-called
melody of death.
So she's manipulating them
with the sound of the flute.
Damn! She's getting
further and further away.
What should I do?!
What is it that I should do?!
Huh?!
This is really looking bad!
Akamaru!
Oh, so you're the real one!
Multiple Fists Barrage!
One more!
My brother and I get along very well.
Usually my older brother Ukon
sleeps inside of me
but when there's a fight
he comes out and helps out.
This is this guy's ability.
Ukon can stick out
his arms, legs and his head
from anywhere in my body
and attacks or defends.
Like this you see...
Multiple Legs Barrage!
It's a three-legged kick.
Works well, doesn't it?
So next it's...!
There's no time to waste, Sakon.
We'll finish this quickly!
Get into the second state!
All right, all right...
You're too impatient, aniki.
I see you're saying those horns
aren't just for display, huh?
As soon as that right one came out,
his Chakra increased
by several tenfold.
Crap!
It seemed hopeless before
but now it's really bad.
What's your liking, aniki?
In pieces.
So now,
perhaps it's time to get serious.
I'll take care of you all at once.
Such confident words!
But those are my lines!
Crap! These guys are persistent!
But it's starting to
get clearer to me.
But the problem is
from here on out.
Damn! Am I completely out of hands?
What?! You're saying
we're gonna do that?!
No, Akamaru!
It's too dangerous to do it here
without our comrades!
You understand, don't you?
If we use that Jutsu,
both you and I will use up
most of our Chakra
and won't be able to move.
If we miss, we'll die here in vain.
Akamaru...
What a pitiful master I am...
that you had to bite me.
I understand, Akamaru.
Just like you said
we only have that left!
Wolf Fang Over Fang!
Now, Akamaru!
What?!
Do it well... Akamaru!
Show them the results of the training!
It's Dynamic Marking!
Playing dirty like that!
All preparations are done!
Inuzuka-Style!
Man-Beast Transformation Combo!
Two-Headed Wolf!
I wondered what it was going
to be and
it turned out to be
a drooling runt of a dog.
What can a dog like this do?
Take this!
Drool?!
Sakon, what're you doing!
To the right!
Damn!
Wolf Fang Over Fang!
Heh! How's that!
Wolf Fang Over Fang revolution speed
is too fast.
It's such an intense high revolution that
even our visibility becomes zero.
Even without direct contact
flesh is cut...
A direct hit from the blow
and you're in pieces.
Really... getting carried away...
This is perfect.
We were just thinking of separating soon.
What?! He divided into two people?!
It's true...
Had we fully received the blow as one
it would've been bad but...
The real battle begins now.
Damn it...
Yeah... I know, Akamaru.
One more shot of
Wolf Fang Over Fang.
The next one is our limit.
We'll take them down with this!
Wolf Fang Over Fang!
It's no use hiding!
I told you we don't chase
with our eyes!
We attack by chasing smells
we've marked with our noses!
— A!
— Un!
— Summoning...
— Rashomon!
That's an impressive power...
To turn Rashomon,
the ultimate shield to protect
Orochimaru-sama into this shape.
But...
— This is the end!
Akamaru!
Akamaru...
To protect me, you...
Damn! He did it again!
My eyes...!
Damn!
Damn...!
This time it's not ordinary piss!
It feels like my eyes are burning
with strong acid!
Where's the other one?!
Hey...
Who are you looking for?
I'll take care of the rest.
Go wash your eyes in that river.
This is my ability...
specialized in assassination of course.
You can't beat me by
just having a good nose and nails.
You can't beat my ability!
You know that the Chakra Network
through which Chakra flows
is deeply interwoven with each
internal organ, right?
The Chakra Network is interwoven
in a variety of complicated ways
and is linked to the tissues that
make up each organ.
Also to each cell that makes up
the tissues
as well as even to proteins
which are the main component of cells...
At the second state,
I can dismantle or reconstruct these cells
or proteins as I wish by using Chakra.
To put it simply,
I can turn my body into tiny pieces,
enter my opponent's body...
return to my original form
and come back out.
Akamaru...
I'm sorry... Akamaru...!
We've always done things together...
we were together
always and everywhere.
Yahoo! Good boy, Akamaru!
Yahoo! We're lucky that the people
who got into our trap had the Earth Scroll!
With our luck like this
we'll reach the goal first.
Akamaru is frightened
all of a sudden.
He can smell the strength of
an opponent's Chakra.
I've never seen him this scared...
The people fighting over there must
be something..
The Seventh Round Battle.
Uzumaki Naruto vs Inuzuka Kiba.
Hey! First of all, don't you bring
a puppy in here!
He'll get in the way of our battle!
Idiot! Akamaru is fighting along with me!
Now then...
Let's go, Akamaru!
Eat this!
There!
Naruto... I'm taking Akamaru back.
Wh-What?! What did you feed him?
His coating has changed to red!
That's why his name is Akamaru.
Let's go, Akamaru!
Beast Mimicry Ninja Art:
Man-Beast Clone!
Let's go! All-Four...
Jutsu!
An opening!
Take this!
Man-Beast Ultimate Taijutsu!
Fang Over Fang!
Akamaru!
Here, Food Pills.
Akamaru! Human Mimicry Ninja Art!
Fang Over Fang!
However, this one time
I'm sunk...
My cells can swim inside
your body as I wish
and I can even create parts
that are only you.
In other words,
a little bit of a fusion condition.
A sharing of the flesh is what it'll be.
A sharing?
That's right... and a cruel way
of killing that only I can accomplish...
The gradual scraping away
of just your cells.
I see.
If that's the case...!
If I do this, what's gonna happen?
Suicide?! That's ridiculous!
Die with me...
hajimete kimi to shabetta
for the first time I spoke to you
kimi wa waratte kureta
and you smiled
hajimete kimi to shabereta
for the first time I was able to speak
boku no kono kotoba de
in my own words
boku nanka ga shaberi kaketara meiwaku ni omou ka na
would you think it was a bother if I approached you?
sonna fuan o kakaete yuuki o dashite mita yo
despite my doubts I worked up my courage
umaku shaberenai boku no fukiyou na hanashi
my clumsy attempts with words
kimi wa mimi o sorasazu ni chanto kiite kureta yo
you listened without turning away
sore dake de boku wa ukarete shimau no sa
no wonder I get carried away by you
dakedo kimi wa boku nante nantomo omottenai yo ne
but you don't feel anything for me do you?
setsunai yo
I feel so sad
dakedo
but...
hajimete kimi to shabetta
for the first time I spoke to you
kimi wa waratte kureta
and you smiled
hajimete kimi to shabereta
for the first time I was able to speak
boku no kono kotoba de
in my own words
hajimete kimi to shabetta
for the first time I spoke to you
kimi wa waratte kureta
and you smiled
hajimete kimi to shabereta
for the first time I was able to speak
boku no kono kotoba de
In my own words
hajimete kimi to shabetta
for the first time I spoke to you
What is this guy?
Kekkei Genkai?!
Damn it! I've never heard
or seen this kind of technique!
Despite the fact that
this many are attacking him,
my attacks don't even faze him!
I don't know if it's
the "Five Dances" or what
but I'll take care of them all!
Next time:
"Everyone's Fight."